{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","address":"3711 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hal","licenseNumber":"055112","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/27/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000BCD8D4A9CDC354C0700D8D10A62C4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41108","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","inspectionDate":"2017-12-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41108","inspectionDate":"12/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 180 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"inspectionid":"41108","inspectionDate":"12/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Plumbing lines","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"41105","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","inspectionDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37565","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","inspectionDate":"2016-12-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"2","pfcount":"3","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"3-202.12","violationDescription":"FOOD may not contain unAPPROVED FOOD ADDITIVES or ADDITIVES or pesticide residues that exceed amounts specified by LAW. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food additive(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"UNAPPROVED ADDITIVE","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"3-502.11","violationDescription":"A FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall obtain a VARIANCE from the REGULATORY AUTHORITY for any specialized processing methods. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Specialized processing methods","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not have a variance","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"UNAPPROVED PROCEDURE/VARIANCE","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue process till a variance is obtained."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"8-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) Before engaging in an activity that requires a HACCP PLAN, a PERMIT applicant or PERMIT HOLDER shall submit to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY for approval a properly prepared HACCP PLAN as specified under § 8-201.14 and the relevant provisions of this Code if:\r\n(1) Submission of a HACCP PLAN is required according to LAW;\r\n(2) A VARIANCE is required as specified under Subparagraph 3-401.11(D)(3), § 3-502.11, or ¶ 4-204.110(B);\r\n(3) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY determines that a FOOD preparation or processing method requires a VARIANCE based on a plan submittal specified under § 8-201.12, an inspectional finding, or a VARIANCE request.\r\n(B) A PERMIT applicant or PERMIT HOLDER shall have a properly prepared HACCP PLAN as specified under § 3-502.12.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of HACCP/ Variance request","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"EXPIRED DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"37565","inspectionDate":"12/13/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3070","name":"Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall","violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3070"}}